macintoshos.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy @ EveryMac.com

### Privacy Policy @ EveryMac.com

Please read and understand the following privacy statement before using any information or services provided by EveryMac.com, [Everyi.com](http://www.everyi.com/), [EveryiPod.com](http://www.everyipod.com/), [EveryiPhone.com](http://www.everyiphone.com/), and [EveryiPad.com](http://www.everyipad.com/) (hereinafter referred to as "EveryMac.com").

###  Privacy Statement

EveryMac.com believes that your privacy on the Internet, and elsewhere, is of great importance. Because EveryMac.com gathers information about its users, it is important for you, as a user of EveryMac.com, to fully understand the terms and conditions regarding the collection and use of that information. This privacy policy discloses what information is gathered, how it is used, and how you can correct, change, or update this information.

This privacy policy will answer the following questions:

  * What personally identifiable information does EveryMac.com collect?
  * How does EveryMac.com use personally identifiable information?
  * With whom, if anyone, does EveryMac.com share this information?
  * What options are available regarding the collection, use, and distribution of this information?
  * How does EveryMac.com allow one to correct, change, or update this information?
  * What security is in place to minimize the risk of loss, misuse, or alteration of this information?

What personally identifiable information does EveryMac.com collect?

When browsing the EveryMac.com website, the Internet Protocol (IP) address and other generic information about your computer is collected and stored in a log file and with Google Analytics. This information is used to help analyze trends, streamline the performance of the webserver, administer the website, and to gather broad statistical information for aggregate use. However, this information is not intended to be linked to any personally identifiable information.

When you register as an EveryMac.com member, some personal information is collected. During the registration process, EveryMac.com requires you to provide your name and e-mail address, and if you wish to participate in contests, your postal mailing address. At any point where EveryMac.com collects personal information, a link will be provided to this privacy policy.

How does EveryMac.com use personally identifiable information?

EveryMac.com uses any information provided by members to improve the experience of using the website and services provided by EveryMac.com, whether to provide personalized or interactive portions of the site, or to prepare future content that is of greater interest to members. For example, EveryMac.com operates an opt-in mailing list (usually sent bimonthly), which is personalized for each member.

EveryMac.com uses tracking information to determine which portions of the site are more popular than others, but what individual members read is not tracked. Likewise, when a search is performed with the EveryMac.com search engine, the search terms used are recorded, but individual search terms are not connected to individual members. Both of these tracking methods are helpful to determine the relative popularity of individual pages and to improve the accuracy of the search engine, which are beneficial to everyone who uses the site.

EveryMac.com also creates aggregate reports on member demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors, and business partners. This results in advertising campaigns that are more effective for advertisers, and advertising that is more relevant for all users of EveryMac.com. However, EveryMac.com does not track the usage patterns of individual members, and therefore, advertisers, sponsors, and business partners will not be able to tell that a specific user clicked on a particular advertisement by way of EveryMac.com.

With whom, if anyone, does EveryMac.com share this information?

EveryMac.com, and the principal author thereof, is the sole owner of all information collected from the website and services provided by EveryMac.com. EveryMac.com will not sell, share, or rent any personally identifiable information to any third-parties, except under specific circumstances, as described below.

**Contest Winners:** In the event that you win a prize from EveryMac.com, you will be notified of winning, and permission will be requested to provide your name, e-mail address, and postal mailing address to the sponsoring company, so they can ship your prize to you. Obviously, if your postal mailing address is not shared, you will not be able to receive your prize, as it has to be shipped to you. Nevertheless, you will be given the option of declining your prize. If you do not win a prize in an EveryMac.com contest, your information will not be shared. However, aggregate member demographic information is shared with contest sponsors.

**Legal:** In the event that you are allegedly involved in any type of criminal activity using the EveryMac.com website, app, or services, and EveryMac.com is subpoenaed to release your membership information, EveryMac.com is required by law to comply with the subpoena. EveryMac.com also reserves the right to disclose membership information in special cases when releasing the information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against any individual who has blatantly or repeatedly violated the Terms of Use agreement.

EveryMac.com does not sell or rent information about individual users to anyone for any reason. However, EveryMac.com does share aggregate demographic information with advertisers, sponsors, and business partners, but this information is not linked to any personal information that could identify any individual person. However, in the event that EveryMac.com or substantially all of its assets are acquired, member information will be one of the transferred assets.

What options are available regarding the collection, use, and distribution of this information?

When you signed up to become a member of EveryMac.com, you were given the option of joining a personalized mailing list, usually sent bimonthly, to inform you of site updates. Only EveryMac.com will send you these personalized e-mail messages, and only if you indicated that you were interested in receiving these messages when you signed up. If you are not interested in receiving site update notices, do not request them when you sign up, or at any time, you can easily leave the list by using the provided instructions.

Companies that advertise on EveryMac.com may use cookies or other means to track advertising performance. While EveryMac.com uses cookies to store login information, cookies received with advertisements are collected by the advertising companies, and EveryMac.com does not have any access to this information.

EveryMac.com provides advertisers, sponsors, and business partners with aggregate information only, in such a manner that neither the client nor EveryMac.com can associate any individual or their associated membership profile within the aggregate information.

Again, EveryMac.com does not sell or rent information about individual users to anyone for any reason, but in the event that EveryMac.com or substantially all of its assets are acquired, member information will be one of the transferred assets.

How does EveryMac.com allow one to correct, change, or update this information?

EveryMac.com makes it simple to correct, change, or update user information via e-mail. If you need to correct, change, or update any of your membership information, please follow these instructions. 

To change your **mailing list status** , send a message entitled " **Join Notification List** " (without the quotes), if you wish to join the list, or " **Leave Notification List** " (without the quotes), if you wish to leave the list, from your registered e-mail address to members "at" everymac "daht" com (replace "at" with @ and "daht" with a ".").

To correct, change, or update your **e-mail address** , send a message entitled " **Change E-mail Address** " (without the quotes) from your existing e-mail address to members "at" everymac "daht" com (replace "at" with @ and "daht" with a ".") with your new e-mail address in the body of the message.

To correct, change, or update your **postal mailing address** , send a message entitled " **Change Postal Address** " (without the quotes), from your registered e-mail address to members "at" everymac "daht" com (replace "at" with @ and "daht" with a ".") with your new postal mailing address in the body of the message. 

What security is in place to minimize the risk of loss, misuse, or alteration of this information?

EveryMac.com takes every precaution to protect your personal information both online and offline. Online the servers that EveryMac.com use are kept in a secured environment, behind a firewall in a secured building. For increased security, only the information needed to login is stored online, while more sensitive information is stored offline in a password-protected database on a password-protected computer.

Although EveryMac.com takes every possible precaution with personal information, all visitors shall follow standard security procedures when accessing and using the EveryMac.com website, app, and services provided by EveryMac.com. By using the website, you acknowledge that EveryMac.com has neither responsibility for nor control of the communications lines used to access the website and services since such lines are provided by a third-party public utility, and that the security of transmissions to and from the website and services are not the responsibility of EveryMac.com.

Privacy Statement Notice & Changes

All members of EveryMac.com should be aware that the EveryMac.com website includes links to other sites. Please be aware that EveryMac.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. It is in your own best interest to be aware when you leave the EveryMac.com website and to read the privacy policies of each website that collects personally identifiable information from its visitors. The privacy policy posted on EveryMac.com applies only to EveryMac.com.

EveryMac.com reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time. In the event that a decision is made to significantly change the privacy policy, a notice regarding the change will be posted on the EveryMac.com homepage so that you will always be aware of what information EveryMac.com collects, how it is used, and under what circumstances, if any, it is disclosed. If at any point EveryMac.com decides to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, you, and all other members, will be notified by email. All members will have a choice as to whether or not EveryMac.com uses their information in this different manner. EveryMac.com will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If you have any additional questions regarding EveryMac.com and your privacy, please use the Contact form. Thank you for supporting EveryMac.com!

<< Back Home

EveryMac.com is provided "as is" without warranty of any kind whatsoever. EveryMac.com, and the author thereof, shall not be held responsible or liable, under any circumstances, for any damages resulting from the use or inability to use the information within. For complete disclaimer and copyright information please read and understand the Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy before using EveryMac.com. Use of any content or images without expressed permission is not allowed, although links to any page are welcomed and appreciated.
